<!--
  ~ Copyright (c) 2018
  ~ Terry Doerksen
  ~ https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/
  ~
  -->

<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Mech Sheets</string>
    <string name="nav_overview">Overview</string>
    <string name="nav_armor">Armor</string>
    <string name="nav_components">Components</string>
    <string name="components_title">Components</string>
    <string name="armor_h">Head\n%1$d \\ %2$d</string>
    <string name="armor_ct">Center Torso\n%1$d \\ %2$d</string>
    <string name="armor_lt">Left Torso\n%1$d \\ %2$d</string>
    <string name="armor_rt">Right Torso\n%1$d \\ %2$d</string>
    <string name="armor_la">Left Arm\n%1$d \\ %2$d</string>
    <string name="armor_ra">Right Arm\n%1$d \\ %2$d</string>
    <string name="armor_ll">Left Leg\n%1$d \\ %2$d</string>
    <string name="armor_rl">Right Leg\n%1$d \\ %2$d</string>
    <string name="armor_title">Armor</string>
    <string name="armor_rear">Rear</string>
    <string name="armor_internal">Internal</string>
    <string name="components_left_arm">Left Arm</string>
    <string name="components_left_torso">Left Torso</string>
    <string name="components_left_leg">Left Leg</string>
    <string name="components_right_arm">Right Arm</string>
    <string name="components_right_torso">Right Torso</string>
    <string name="components_right_leg">Right Leg</string>
    <string name="components_head">Head</string>
    <string name="components_center_torso">Center Torso</string>
    <string name="overview_title">Overview</string>
    <string name="overview_name">Name: %1$s</string>
    <string name="overview_tons">Tons: %1$d</string>
    <string name="overview_walking">Walking: %1$d</string>
    <string name="overview_running">Running: %1$d</string>
    <string name="overview_jumping">Jumping: %1$d</string>
    <string name="overview_equipment">Equipment</string>
    <string name="overview_heatsinks">Heatsinks: %1$d / %2$d remaining</string>
    <string name="overview_pilot_details">Pilot Details</string>
    <string name="overview_pilot_skill">Piloting: %1$d</string>
    <string name="overview_gunnery_skill">Gunnery: %1$d</string>
    <string name="overview_pilots_hits">Hits Taken: %1$d</string>
    <string name="overview_heat_scale">Heat Scale: %1$d</string>
    <string name="main_title">To load a Mech, choose one of the buttons below.  If you are new to this app, choose the "Import from a Collection" option to get started</string>
    <string name="overview_ammo">%1$s: %2$d Shots Fired</string>
    <string name="overview_description">Notes</string>
    <string name="overview_save">Save</string>
    <string name="spinner_value_none">[Add]</string>
    <string name="overview_delete">Delete</string>
    <string name="overview_confirm_delete">Are you sure you want to PERMANENTLY REMOVE the %1$s?</string>
    <string name="main_units_loaded">There are %1$d units loaded</string>
    <string name="menu_about">About</string>
    <string name="title_activity_about">About</string>
    <string name="libraries">3rd Party Libraries</string>
    <string name="legal_gson">Use of the GSON Library is used under the Apache 2.0 License - a link to the project and license is below.</string>
    <string name="version">Version: %1$s (build %2$d)</string>
    <string name="website_apache">http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0</string>
    <string name="website_gson">https://github.com/google/gson</string>
    <string name="website_material_icons">https://github.com/google/material-design-icons</string>
    <string name="website_creative_common">http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by/4.0/</string>
    <string name="legal_material_icons">Use of the Material Icons are used under the Creative Common Attribution 4.0 International License (CC-BY 4.0) - links to the project and license are:</string>
    <string name="legal">Legal</string>
    <string name="legal_contents">
        The Mech Sheets application is (and will remain) a non-commercial, open source application (released under CC-BY-NC-4.0 license) designed to make game play of the Classic BattleTech table top game (by Catalyst Game Labs) easier when paper record sheets are not an option.   This application is fan made to make the authors life easier and hopefully can be of use to others. \n
\n
The above mentioned license covers only the application and it\’s source code - Classic BattleTech, BattleTech, BattleMech, \‘Mech, and MechWarrior are registered trademarks and/or trademarks of The Topps Company, Inc. in the United States and/or other countries.   All rights reserved to the appropriate owners and original content creators. I have received permission to use the above terms and make this application available to others free of charge.  Any issues please contact me and I will make the appropriate adjustments and corrections.  Thank you. \n
\n
Mech Sheets software License - Copyright 2018 Terry Doerksen:
    </string>
    <string name="license_url">https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/legalcode\n\n\n\n\n\n</string>
    <string name="overview_movementtorso_twist">Torso Twist</string>
    <string name="overview_twist_front">Center</string>
    <string name="overview_twist_left">Left</string>
    <string name="overview_twist_right">Right</string>
    <string name="help_main">
        <![CDATA[
            <h1>Help: Starting Out</h1>
            <p>To start using this app, you will need MTF files copied to your phone.  MTF files come from the excellent PC game MegaMek:<br/><br/>
            1) Download and extract the latest version of MegaMek to your computer.<br/>
            2) Find the MTF files included with MegaMek.<br/>
            3) Copy the MTF files to your device.<br/>
            4) Click on the giant + symbol and find the mechs you want.<br/><br/>
            Note: If you copied the MTF files to your devices external SD Card you may have to tap on the menu button at the top left of the Files window and tap Show SD Card.
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="help_armor">
        <![CDATA[
            <h1>Help: Armor</h1>
            <p>When a mech takes damage, use this screen to record damage to each locations armor and internal structure.<br/><br/>
            <b>Single Tap:</b> Each single tap will reduce the armor in that location by 1.<br/>
            <b>Long Tap:</b> Holding your finger down on a location will restore that location by 1 point.<br/><br/>
            When that location is destroyed, the color will change to red.
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="help_components">
        <![CDATA[
            <h1>Help: Components</h1>
            <p>When a mech takes critical damage, use this screen to record damage to each component that is hit.<br/><br/>
            <b>Single Tap:</b> Each single tap will destroy that component in that location.<br/>
            <b>Long Tap:</b> Holding your finger down on a destroyed component will return it to functional status.<br/><br/>
            When a component is destroyed, it will affect the Overview screen - for example destroying a weapon here will disable it in the Overview screen.  Damaging a leg will reduce it\'s indicated speed.  When a component is destroyed, the color will change to red.
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="help_overview">
        <![CDATA[
            <h1>Help: Overview</h1>
            <p>This shows the overview of your unit.  As leg or jump jet damage occurs, the blue Walk/Run/Jump values will turn red and be reduced.
            <h1>Help: Equipment</h1>
            <p>Weapons can be tapped on to help you remember what weapons you are firing.  If a weapon is destroyed, it will be grayed out.  Tapping [ALL] will either select or deselect all weapons.<br/>
            <p>Each ton of ammo appears as a button that you can click on each time the weapon is fired.
            <p>As heat sinks are destroyed, the remaining heat sinks counter will adjust and will turn red.  Use the Heat Scale to track how much heat the mech currently has.
            <h1>Help: Pilot Details</h1>
            <b>Single Tap:</b> Each single tap will increase the Piloting or Gunnery skill value by 1.<br/>
            <b>Long Tap:</b> Holding down your finger on the button will decrease the Piloting or Gunnery skill value by 1.<br/><br/>
            <p>As the Mechwarrior takes damage, adjust the Hits Taken slider accordingly to keep track.<br/><br/>
            <p>Notes can be used to enter in whatever information you wish.  TAP SAVE WHEN DONE!
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="invalid_file_format">
        <![CDATA[
            <h1>Invalid File!</h1>
            <p>This does not appear to be a supported file format.  If this should be a valid file, please contact me and provide me the MTF file you were trying to load.
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="all">[ALL]</string>
    <string name="menu_help">Help</string>
    <string name="overview_reset">Reset</string>
    <string name="overview_confirm_reset">This will reset this %1$s back to stock - fully repaired - status.  This will reset:\n\n
        - Equipment selection\n
        - Ammo used\n
        - Heat Level\n
        - Armor / Internal Damage\n
        - Individual components\n
        \n
        Are you sure you want this?</string>
    <string name="armor_destroyed">CRITICAL! Damage has transferred to the internal structure!</string>
    <string name="armor_rear_destroyed">CRITICAL! Damage has transferred to the internal structure!</string>
    <string name="location_maxed">You are exceeding the maximum default value</string>
    <string name="internal_destroyed">The internal structure in this location has been completely destroyed!</string>

    <string name="previous">Previous</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="selection">Selection</string>
    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="description">Description</string>
    <string name="component_view_name">%1$d) %2$s</string>
    <string name="load">Load</string>
    <string name="download">Download</string>
    <string name="mega_mek_path">https://github.com/MegaMek/megamek/releases/download/v0.49.11/megamek-windows-0.49.11.zip</string>
    <string name="mechs_file">megamek-windows-0.49.11/data/mechfiles/mechs.zip</string>
    <string name="dest_megamek">megamek.zip</string>
    <string name="title_activity_mech_detail_host">MechDetailHostActivity</string>
    <string name="title_mech_list">Mechs</string>
    <string name="title_mech_detail">Mech Detail</string>
    <string name="open_importer">Import from a Collection</string>
    <string name="add_single">(Legacy) Add a single MTF entry</string>
</resources>
